A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller papers FA002
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, C; 34.4 cubic ft. 86 boxes
  - Business Investments, I; 6.0 cubic ft. 15 boxes
    - Colgate, James B. & Company, 1882-July 1885; 130.0 pages (Reel 2, Frame 113, Box 73, Folder 544)
      New York, New York. Brokers; instructions from John D. Rockefeller; notices of debits and credits of John D. Rockefeller's accounts' changing interest rates; lists of securities John D. Rockefeller kept at company; lobbying efforts for railroad bills; material on "Oregon Transportation Contest" involving Charles F. Adams, B. Ives, E. Smith, and the Union Pacific, etc.; the rate war between the western railroads.
    - Colgate, James B. & Company, August 1885-October 1886; 104.0 pages (Box 73, Folder 545, Reel 2, Frame 0243)
    - Colgate, James B. & Company, November 1886-April 1889; 117.0 pages (Box 73, Folder 546, Reel 2, Frame 0347)
    - Colgate, James B. & Company, May 1889-1893; 102.0 pages (Box 73, Folder 547, Reel 2, Frame 0464)
    - Collins - Corrigan, 49.0 pages (Box 74, Folder 548, Reel 2, Frame 0566)
      Collins, R. E., 2/8/1892. New York, New York. Rail investment; inventions. Collins, H. D. & Company, 12/10/1890. Mount Vernon, New York. Wholesale lumber; offered lands. Colorado Fuel & Iron Company, 7/14/1893. New York, New York. William Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller memorandum on stock and dividends. Colton, George, 1888-1892. New York, New York. Natural Gas Trust; dividend notices. Combs, A. H. & Company, 2/28/1893. New York, New York. Broker; sought John D. Rockefeller's business. Comstock, Theodore, 10/20/1890. Austin, Texas. Trying to form syndicate to buy and sell Texas land; Geological Survey of Texas. Conant, L. H., 11/28-30/1891. New York, New York. Offering Chicago & Erie bonds; broker. Condit, H. C., 3/1/1887. Newark, New Jersey. Gas machine investment. Continental Trust Company, undated. New York, New York. Seeking deposits. Cook, E. M., 5/4/1889. New York, New York. Cartaret Chemical Company; offering Brooklyn real estate. Cook, Samuel G. B., 4/20/1889. Baltimore, Maryland. Has patents for fiber manufacturing process; needs capital. Cooke, W. J., 9/30/1887. Chicago, Illinois. Sending John D. Rockefeller a lease. Cooksey, George, 8/1/1887. New York, New York. George B. Cooksey & Company successor to David Dows, Jr. & Company; formation of grain, flour and provision commission business. Coolidge, Henry, 7/7/1883. New York, New York. Truman & Coolidge, bankers and brokers; Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railroad Company Northern Pacific Railroad Company bonds. Corbett, Edward, 11/8/1890. Washington, D. C. Mechanical Engineer; offers stock in flour mill manufacturing company. Corbin, Austin, 3/20-26/1890. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, and New York, New York. Philadelphia & Reading Railroad Company; Howard Potter of Brown Brothers & Company letter on problems of railroads; investor relations. Corrigan, James, 1888-1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Franklin Iron Mine; Aurora Iron Mining Company; Standard Oil Company; payments on John D. Rockefeller's loan to him; steamship owner.
    - Cowles, D. S., 1881-1883; 73.0 pages (Box 74, Folder 549, Reel 2, Frame 0615)
      New York, New York. Worked for William Rockefeller's office; stock market speculation; subscription for Union Pacific Railroad stock; relations with R. P. Flower & Company, Jesup & Lamont, J. B. Colgate & Company, and other brokers John D. Rockefeller did business with; information on various stocks and bonds and the state of John D. Rockefeller's accounts; recommendations regarding stock offers, the state of the market, advising John D. Rockefeller to "whoop" up slow market; much material on 1886 slump and proposed remedies; Republic of Honduras timberlands venture; Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul Railroad Company stock; purchase and sale of Standard Oil Trust stock; Ann Arbor & Northern Michigan Railroad purchase.
    - Cowles, D. S., 1884-1885; 132.0 pages (Box 74, Folder 550, Reel 2, Frame 0688)
    - Cowles, D. S., 1886-1887; 92.0 pages (Reel 2, Frame 0829, Box 74, Folder 551)
    - Cowles, J. G. W., 1886-1893; 79.0 pages (Box 74, Folder 552, Reel 2, Frame 0912)
      Cleveland, Ohio. Real estate and loan broker; Gallup allotment; Edwin Jackson deed; loan opportunities for John D. Rockefeller; John D. Rockefeller's purchase of Cleveland properties; N. K. Foster mortgage and release.
    - Crandall - Curtiss, 36.0 pages (Reel 3, Frame 0001, Box 74, Folder 553)
      Crandall, L. A., 1889-1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Euclid Avenue Baptist Church pastor; payments on John D. Rockefeller's loan to him. Crane, C. R., 6/4/1890. Detroit, Michigan. National Tag Company; seeks John D. Rockefeller capital. Crane, J. S., 5/20/1882. New York, New York. Seeking John D. Rockefeller's business on stock exchange. Crane, Theron I., 1/2/1891. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Crane & Schuyler, commission merchants; notice of formation of partnership. Crawford, W., 8/9/1889. New York, New York. Natural Gas Trust certificates of John D. Rockefeller. Cromwell, William N., 1/5/1891. New York, New York. Decker, Howell & Company assignee; company's resumption of business. Crooker, Mr., 12/15/1893. New York, New York. Memorandum on arrangements with lobbyist in Washington, D. C. Cross, H. C., 5/10/?. Unidentified location. Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway Company receiver; H. K. Enos memorandum on him. Croton Company Limited, 1884. New York, New York. Subscription agreement. Cruikshank, E. A. & Company, 10/21/1884. New York, New York. Offering Fifth Avenue property. Cullen & Newman, 1/12/1891. Knoxville, Tennessee. Importers, wholesalers of china and silver; Coal Creek Mining & Manufacturing Company opportunity. Winthrop Cunningham & Sons, 1/25/1890. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Santo Domingo sugar business proposal. Curtiss, W. H., 1891. New York, New York. John D. Rockefeller loans to and from Jesup & Lamont; Standard Oil Company employee; accounting methods.
    - Da Costa - Dodge, 92.0 pages (Box 74, Folder 554, Reel 3, Frame 0037)
      Da Costa, A. M., 10/1886-1889. New York, New York, and Kansas City, Missouri. Wants John D. Rockefeller's participation in building railroad depot in Kansas City; John D. Rockefeller declined. Damon, H. G., 6/10/1890. Corsicana, Texas. Land development investment offer. Daniel, E. B., 8/10/1889. Chanute, Kansas. Flax fibre factory investment offer. Daniel & Armat, 1892. Washington, D. C. Real estate in Newport News, Virginia. Darrow, F. V., 2/12/1890. Minneapolis, Minnesota. Fruit farm investment offer in California. Date, John J., 1891-1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Broker; offers bank and iron company shares. Davis, John H. & Company, 3/1889-7/1893. New York, New York. Broker, investment offers; report on 1893 panic; railroad stocks; American Meat Company; St. Paul City Railway Company. Day, H. S., 5/13/1890. New York, New York. Coal mines investment offer in Pennsylvania. de Cordova, Aaron, 1889-1893. New York, New York. Introduced by Alfredo de Cordova, banker and broker; asked help in 1893 with financial problems. DeForrest Land & Improvement Company; 7/19/1890. Chicago, Illinois. Real estate offer. "Delaware," 8/16/1882. New York, New York. Coded message on loan rates. Delaware, Lackawanna & Western Railroad Company, 1888-1889. New York, New York. Annual earnings statements. DeLong, M. B., 6/7/1890. Utica, New York. Plan for control of window glass industry. Deming, C. C., 2/1/1889. New York, New York. Sending bond coupons of Florida Construction Company. Deming, H. C., 2/27/1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Broker; offer to buy bank stocks. Denny, H. St. C., 9/1890-1/1893. Buffalo, New York. Offer of Buffalo General Electric bonds; D. O'Day affiliate. Denver & Rio Grande Western Railway Company, 1/8/1886. New York, New York. Call for outstanding bonds. De Selding Brothers, 3/16/1891. New york, New York. Request for loan for hotel project by real estate brokers. Des Marets, E. A., 11/1888. New York, New York. San Miquel Gold Placers Company of Colorado, gold mine investment offer. Dick Brothers & Company, 1/22/1892. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Brokers; Metropolitan Traction Company stock offer. Dillon, Sidney, 7/22/1881. New York, New York. Offer of stock in Oregon Short Line Railway Company to holders of stock in Union Pacific Company. Dodd, S. C. T., 10/25/1887. New York, New York. Coded telegram concerning unidentified testimony. Dodge, H., 9/1892. New York, New York. Land development offer near Seattle, Washington; wants to start commission business there.
    - Dominick & Dickerman, 1882-1893; 121.0 pages (Reel 3, Frame 0129, Box 74, Folder 555)
      New York, New York. Bankers & brokers; cipher codes; John D. Rockefeller attempts to purchase seat on New York Stock Exchange; market conditions; interest rates; account balances; railroad stocks; Southern Chemical Company.
    - Donald - Dyer, 133.0 pages (Reel 3, Frame 0250, Box 75, Folder 556)
      Donald, James W., 1892. New York, New York. Dividend payments; Hanover National Bank. "Dorcas," 11/18/1888. New York, New York. Code name; message on unidentified company stock. Dougan, D. H., 7/13/1889. Leadville, Colorado. Offers of Distillers & Cattle Feeders Trust stock. Douglass, A. E., 4/2/1889. Kansas City, Missouri. Offer of mortgage loans in Kansas City. Douglass, J. L., 1/25/1890. New York, New York. Offer of real estate next to Standard Oil Company office. Dow, Myron C., 11/10/1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Mill investment opportunity. Dowling, G. DeWitt, 3/25/1892. Hightstown, New Jersey. Request for money on account from ministry student being helped by John D. Rockefeller. Dowling, G. T., 7/1888-10/1891. Cleveland, Ohio, and Albany, New York. Statement of account on deposit with John D. Rockefeller; pastor of Euclid Avenue Baptist Church. Downs, J. L., 3/12/1891. New York, New York. Describes South Dakota "wind cave" [Wind Cave National Park]. Dows, David & Company, 12/1886-1/1887. New York, New York. John D. Rockefeller wheat speculation on Duluth, Minnesota market. Drake, A. A., 6/10/1889. New York, New York. Offers services as broker. Drayton, J. C., 3/4/1891. New York, New York. Rapid transit offer. Drexel Harjes & Company, 9/18/1889. Paris, France. Repeats cable from George D. Rogers while John D. Rockefeller in Rome, Italy. Duff, Samuel, 7/26-8/9/1889. Steubenville, Ohio. Coal and oil lands investment offer in Pennsylvania. Duluth & Iron Range Railroad Company, 3/26/1888. New York, New York. Interest payment on bonds. Duncan, Rev. S. W., 1882. Cincinnati, Ohio. John D. Rockefeller handled securities transaction for him. Duncan & Tarbox, 8/26/1891. Arcola, Illinois. Farm investment offers. Dunn, B. L., 12/26/1889. New York, New York. Inventor of device for running locomotives on gas. Durgin, G. W., 3/3/1886. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Lead mine investment offer in Missouri. Duval, H. C., 1887-1894. New York, New York. Personal loan by John D. Rockefeller; New York Central & Hudson River Railroad Company employee; Joliet Steel Company shareholder; interest in employee of Lombard Ayers Tide Water Pipe Line. Dyer, H. B. & Company, 4/22/1887. New York, New York. Business & financial broker; offers staple manufacturing business in Maryland.
    - Earl - Emerson & Turnbull, 74.0 pages (Reel 3, Frame 0383, Box 75, Folder 557)
      Earl, W. M., 11/23/1888. New York, New York. Offering brokerage service. East End Savings Bank company, 10/7/1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Statement. East Tennessee, Virginia & Georgia Railway Company, 1889. New York, New York. Bond offering; Richmond & West Point Terminal Railway & Warehouse Company. Ebert, R., 8/30/1889. Fon du Lac, Wisconsin. Offers timberlands for sale. Eddy, J. W., 5/28/1891. Helena, Montana. Wants aid for proposed college in Helena. Edison General Electric Company, undated. Unidentified location. Newspaper report. Edmundson, D. G., 8/1889-5/1891. Des Moines, Iowa. William Rockefeller investment in Security Loan & Trust Company. Edwards, J. S., 3/17/1891. Seattle, Washington. Offers land near Seattle. Edwards, W., 4/15/1889-4/1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Held John D. Rockefeller proxy in Cleveland Driving Park Company. Eells, D. P., 6/1888-1/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Banker and friend; investment offer; Otis Iron & Steel Company. Ellery, G. B., 9/26/1889. New York, New York. Stock purchase offer. Elliott, D., 2/1893-8/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Payments on note. Ellis, E., 2/1889-5/1890. New York, New York. Oregon & Transcontinental Company treasurer; cashed John D. Rockefeller's coupons. Ellis, H., 9/16/1893. New York, New York. Offered zinc and iron mines investment in New Jersey. Emerson, R. H., 3/18/1887. New York, New York. Investment opportunity. Emerson & Turnbull, 5/1/1890. New York, New York. Moving notice; bankers and brokers.
    - Enos, H. K., 1885-October 1886; 153.0 pages (Reel 3, Frame 0457, Box 75, Folder 558)
      New York, New York. Brokerage firm; handled John D. Rockefeller investment in Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway Company, Chicago and Northwestern Railroad Company and other railroad stocks; market conditions; cipher codes.
    - Enos, H. K., November 1886-1887; 133.0 pages (Box 75, Folder 559, Reel 3, Frame 0610)
    - Enos, H. K., 1888-July 1889; 127.0 pages (Box 75, Folder 560, Reel 3, Frame 0743)
    - Enos, H. K., November 1889-1891; 55.0 pages (Box 75, Folder 561, Reel 3, Frame 0870)
    - Epply - Evans, 26.0 pages (Box 75, Folder 562, Reel 3, Frame 0925)
      Epply, John P., 1888. Cincinnati, Ohio. Mining stock; Milton, West Virginia, Coal & Mining Company. Ertz, Charles E., 1892. New York, New York. Railroad bonds in California. Euclid Avenue National Bank, 1886-1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Bank stock. Evans, O., 2/1891-3/1891. Oakland, Alabama. Oil lands offer.
    - Fahnestock - Flagler, 112.0 pages (Reel 3, Frame 0951, Box 76, Folder 563)
      Fahnestock, H. C., 2/1886-12/29/1889. New York, New York. Asking John D. Rockefeller to join in Richmond & West Point Terminal Railway & Warehouse Company financing; investment offers in railroads; First National Bank. Fahnestock & Company, 4/1890. New York, New York. Broker; offer of railroad bonds. Farmer, E. J., 8/1890-2/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Investment offer in Colorado silver mines. Fasig, W. B., 10/1887-10/1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Cleveland Driving Park Company; dividends. Farson, Leach & Company, 10/1889. New York, New York. Bonds for sale. Faurot, B. C., 2/25/1889. New York, New York. Railroad investment offer in northwestern Ohio. Fay, C. N., 12/22/1888. Chicago, Illinois. Offering Minnesota Iron Company stock. Fenn, C. A., 1/1890-6/1890. New York, New York. Offering United States Land & Investment Company securities. Ferris, R. B., 1/27/1893. New York, New York. Scheme for controlling Ohio oil traffic; Wheeling Bridge & Terminal Railway Company. Field, A. A., 10/6/1893. Ashtabula, Ohio. Is John D. Rockefeller in Ashtabula Steel & Land Company? Field, C. W., 12/20/1886. New York, New York. Sends information on elevated railroads. Fifth Avenue Transportation Company, 1886-1890. New York, New York. Meetings; stock ownership. Finney, T. J., 4/22/1890. New York, New York. New York Life Insurance Company salesman. Fischer, F., 8/12/1891. New York, New York. Offer of lumber securities in Mississippi. First National Bank, 12/16/1886. New York, New York. Loan account balance. Fisher, F., 8/17/1887-9/15/1887. New York, New York. Standard Oil Trust dividend signing procedures. Fisher, J. W., 7/31/1889. Newark, New Jersey. Offer of timberlands in Tennessee. Flagg, J. H., 6/1886-12/1889. Washington, D. C., and New York, New York. Lawyer; St. Paul, Minnesota real estate offers; reports on legislation. Flagler, H. M., 1882-1893. New York, New York. Standard Oil Trust stock transfers and dissolution; investments and loans; railroad stocks.
    - Fleming - R. P. Flower & Company, 116.0 pages (Box 76, Folder 564, Reel 4, Frame 0001)
      Fleming, W. L., 11/1889-10/1890. Unidentified location. Loan of $1,000 to Fleming by John D. Rockefeller. Fleming, C., 1890. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Brochure on Allegheny County lands. Freeman, J. F. (misfile), 1889. New York, New York. Treasurer, Standard Oil Company of New York; John D. Rockefeller loans and investments [see also: Folder 569 below]. Fletcher, D., 3/1890. Denver, Colorado. Offer of Denver land. R. P. Flower & Company, 1882-1893. New York, New York. Brokerage firm; John D. Rockefeller accounts; market conditions; railroad stocks.
    - Foote - Freeman, A. A., 83.0 pages (Box 76, Folder 565, Reel 4, Frame 0117)
      Foote, R., 1885-1890. New York, New York. Investment offers; banker and broker. Foote, U. S., 7/9/1892. Unidentified location. Offer to sell California mines to John D. Rockefeller. Ford, F. L., 9/15/1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Loan opportunities; mortgage offerings. Foster, C., 7/7/1888. Fostoria, Ohio. Request for loan. Fowler, W. A., 10/19/1890. New York, New York. Building offer in city. Fox, J. W., 4/25/1887. New York, New York. Coal and timberlands in Virginia and Kentucky. Fox, S. J., 8/6/1891. New York, New York. Road construction project in Florida. Francis, G. W., 10/4/1889. Buffalo, New York. Proposes trust of axe manufacturers. Frazer & Company, undated. New York, New York. Bankers and brokers; offer services. Frech, T. W., 1/31/1890. New York, New York. Offers property in city. Frederick, P. A., 6/26/1893. Kansas City, Missouri. Real estate offer. Freeman, A. A., 1888-1891. New York, New York, and LaCrosse, Wisconsin. Investment offers in Michigan, Minnesota, and Wisconsin; flour mills.
    - Freemen, J. F., October 1881-July 1884; 120.0 pages (Box 76, Folder 566, Reel 4, Frame 0200)
      New York, New York. Treasurer, Standard Oil Company of New York; John D. Rockefeller loans and investments.
    - Freemen, J. F., August 1884-July 1885; 67.0 pages (Reel 4, Frame 0320, Box 76, Folder 567)
    - Freemen, J. F., August 1885-September 1886; 97.0 pages (Box 76, Folder 568, Reel 4, Frame 0387)
    - Freemen, J. F., October 1886-December 1890; 90.0 pages (Reel 4, Frame 0484, Box 76, Folder 569)
      New York, New York. Treasurer, Standard Oil Company of New York; John D. Rockefeller loans and investments. [see also 1890 misfile in Folder 564 above].
    - Fuller, H. A. - Fuller, R. J., 21.0 pages (Reel 4, Frame 0574, Box 76, Folder 570)
      Fuller, H. A., 1890-1891. New York, New York. Investment offers; broker and banker; North East Street Railway Company bonds of Kansas City, Missouri; Ocean Steamship Company of Savannah, Georgia. Fuller, R. J., 3/2/1887. Cleveland, Ohio. Insurance investment offer; Ohio Fidelity & Accident Company.
    - Ga Nun - Giovannini, 111.0 pages (Box 77, Folder 571, Reel 4, Frame 0595)
      Ga Nun, S. M., 6/24/1893. New York, New York. Request for loan. Gallaudet, P. W., 1886-1891. New York, New York. Investment offers; bankers and brokers. Gandil, F. V., 2/9/1888. New York, New York. Broker seeks John D. Rockefeller business. Gardner, H. B., 1887. New York, New York. Real estate offers in city. Gates, W. N. Cleveland, Ohio. Purchases unidentified securities. Gay, C. B., 4/18/1890. New York, New York. Oil railroad investment offer. Geer, E. F., 1882. Buffalo, New York. Rail car for shipping horse; Rochester Driving Association. Geary, D., 7/21/1891. Kansas city, Missouri. Real estate offer. George, Nesbitt & Company, 1881. New York, New York. Office supplies; printing of cipher books. George, James, 6/1893. Newark, New Jersey. Copper plating. German Land & Cattle Company, 1/1/1889. San Francisco, California. Statement of assets, prospectus. Gerstmann, S., 4/20/1888. New York, New York. Investment offer. Gickow, S. W., 3/1/1891. St. Augustine, Florida. Hotel forwarded letters to H. M. Flagler. Giffing, J. F., 7/18/1891. New York, New York. Real estate offer in city. Gilbough, J. W., 1890-1893. New York, New York. Broker; investment offers; municipal bonds. Gilder, Farr & Company, 1888-1890. New York, New York. Brokers; investment offers. Gill, John, 5/10/1892-12/1892. Baltimore, Maryland. Potomac Valley Railroad Company bonds. Gilman & Company, 2/7/1888. St. Paul, Minnesota. Wholesale house; investment offer. Gilsey, A. F., 2/20/1891. New York, New York. Real estate offer in city. Giovannini, Madame, 6/20/1890. New York, New York. Regarding money and bonds she placed with John D. Rockefeller.
    - Gleason - Gruebnther, 79.0 pages (Box 77, Folder 572, Reel 4, Frame 0706)
      Gleason, C. W., 2/16/1893. New York, New York. Request for loan; broker of iron mines. Gleichner, L., 10/18/1891. Pomona, California. Offer of gold and silver mining lands in Arizona. Goble, L. S., 9/16/1890. New York, New York. Insurance premium for W. E. Clarke. Goldman, Leon, 3/21/1892. New York, New York. Seeks interview. Gorham, J. M., 5/5-8/1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Washboard trust plan. Gostling, C. P., 2/3/1893. Bellaire, Ohio. Cement industry investment offer. Gould, George J., 1892. New York, New York. Wabash St. Louis & Pacific Railroad Company proxy; conflict with O. D. Ashley. Gould, Jay, 1889. Unidentified location. Article on plans for Missouri, Kansas & Texas Railway Company and richmond West Point Terminal Railway & Warehouse Company; H. K. Enos. Gracie, A., 4/1892. New York, New York. Investment in irrigation project in Texas. Grady, C. P., 9/1886-9/1890. Baltimore, Maryland, and Duluth, Minnesota. Real estate broker; offers coal and timberlands in West Virginia and iron ore lands in Minnesota and Canada. Graham, E. S., 5/16/1891. Graham, Texas. Railroad investment offer; extension of Missouri, Kansas, & Texas Railway Company. Granger, S. O., 12/22/1891. Cartersville, Georgia. Iron mine offer in Georgia; Etowah Iron Company. Grant Brothers, 1/31/1891. New York, New York. Investment offer. Gray, C. L., 1/28/1892. New York, New York. New York Bank Note Company; wants to bid on New York Transit Company bond engraving and printing. Gray, J. D., 5/14/1890. Astoria, Oregon. Real estate offer for shipbuilding plant. Greenwood, A. G., 7/24/1893. Chicago, Illinois. Offers gold mine investment in South Dakota. Gregory, G. F., 2/10/1888. New York, New York. Standard Oil Company, domestic trade department; railroad scheme of Dalrymple brothers. Grey, W., 9/1890. London, England. Railroad investment offer in England; Midland Tramways Company. Griffin, A., 3/6/1893. Washington, D. C. Automatic car coupler invention. Grover, W. G., 12/24/1886. Hamer, North Carolina. Mineral investment offer in North Carolina. Grovesteen, W., 8/25/1891. New York, New York. Investment offer. Griscom, C. A., 1889-1892. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Borrowed $220,000 for purchase of Standard Oil Trust shares; International Navigation Company; Northern Pacific Railroad Company construction of whaleback steamers. Griswold, C., 6/19/1885. New York, New York. Steel mill investment offer; Albany & Rensselaer Iron & Steel Company. Gruaz, T., 1889-1890. East St. Louis, Illinois. Coal, salt, and farm lands investment offers in Illinois, Kansas, and Missouri. Guenther, E. G., 10/7/1881. Cleveland, Ohio. Bookbinding receipt.
    - Hagan - Hatch, 137.0 pages (Box 77, Folder 573, Reel 4, Frame 0785)